<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mother and Child</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_user">UserActivity</string>


    <!-- Employee Telemedicine-->

    <string-array name="doctorstype">
        <item>Select</item>
        <item>Gynocologist</item>
        <item>Pediatrician</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="doctorsname">
        <item>Select</item>
        <item>Dr.Rohith</item>
        <item>Dr.Vivek</item>
        <item>Dr.Mrinal</item>
        <item>Dr.Rakesh</item>
        <item>Dr.Swetha</item>
        <item>Dr.Likhitha</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="privatevehicle">
        <item>Select</item>
        <item>7000597375</item>
        <item>8918398210</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="type">
        <item>Select</item>
        <item>Mother</item>
        <item>Child</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="gender">
        <item>Select</item>
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="age">
        <item>Select</item>
        <item>Below 3months</item>
        <item>5-10months</item>
        <item>1-2yrs</item>
        <item>2-5yrs</item>
        <item>Above 5yrs</item>
        <item>Below 30yrs</item>
        <item>30-35yrs</item>
        <item>35-40yrs</item>
        <item>40-45yrs</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="doctor_age">
        <item>Select</item>
        <item>Below 30yrs</item>
        <item>30-35yrs</item>
        <item>35-40yrs</item>
        <item>40-45yrs</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="ngoSupport">
        <item>Select</item>
        <item>7000597375</item>
        <item>8918398210</item>

    </string-array>


    <string-array name="employeeName">
        <item>Select</item>
        <item>Sayan</item>
        <item>Alok</item>
        <item>Prabhat</item>
        <item>Siddharth</item>
        <item>Ajay</item>
        <item>Tukaram</item>
        <item>Aman</item>
        <item>Nisha</item>


    </string-array>

    <string name="INAP">
       It has been launched with an aim to reduce neonatal mortality and stillbirths.\n
1. Pre_Conception and Antenatal Care Intervention Package:Antenatal screening for Anemia and Hypertensive  disorders of pregnancy.\n\n
2. Care during Labour and Childbirth.\n\n
3. Immediate Newborn Care :Interventions to prevent hypothermia,giving Vitamin K supplements at birth.\n\n
4. Care of healthy newborn:Home visits till six weeks by trained ASHA and Clean postnatal practices.\n
5. Care of Small and Sick Newborn:Intensive care services (NICU) at regional level for  Assisted ventilation and Surfactant use.\n\n
6. Care beyond Newborn Survival:Follow up visits of small and low birth weight babies till 2 years of age.

    </string>

    <string name="JSSK">
        This scheme entitles all pregnant women delivering in public health institutions to absolutely free and no expense delivery including Caesarean section.\n\n
MOTHER/PREGNANT WOMEN\n\n
1. Free and cashless  delivery\n
2. Free C section\n
3. ree drugs and consumables\n
4. Free diagnostics\n
5. Free diet during stay in health institutions\n
6. Free provision for blood\n
7. Free transport\n\n
INFANTS\n\n
1. Free treatment\n
2. Free drugs and consumables\n
3. Free diagnostics\n
4. Exemption from user charges\n
5. Free transport\n


    </string>

    <string name="HBNC">
       HBNC through ASHAs has been initiated to improve newborn practices at the community level and early detection and referral of sick newborn babies.\n\n
1. Essential care of the newborn.\n\n
2. Examination of the newborn.\n\n
3. Early recognition of danger sign.\n\n
4. Counselling of mother for breastfeeding.\n\n
5. Immunisation.



    </string>

    <string name="FBNC">
        It amis at different levels to reduce newborn morbidity and mortality by setting up of Special New Born Care Units (SNCUs), Newborn Stabilization Units (NBSUs) and Newborn Care Corners (NBCCs) atdifferent levels is a thrust area under NHM.\n\n
1. Kangaroo Mother Care\n
2. Thermal Protection\n
3. Resuscitation of the Newborn Baby\n
    </string>

    <string name="RBSK">
         RBSK for health screening and early intervention services has been launched to provide comprehensive care to all the children in the age group of 0-18 years in the community.\n\n
1. Screening at Anganwadi level: \n\nScreening by Mobile Block Health teams for deficiencies, diseases, developmental delays including disability at the
 Anganwadi centre at least twice a year.\n\n
2. Screening at Schools:\n\nScreening by Mobile Health teams for deficiencies, diseases, developmental delays including disability, adolescent health at the
                        local schools at least once a year.\n


    </string>

    <string name="firsttrimester">


** Folic acid is an important addition to your diet as it helps sustain and develop the embryo.\n\n
1.Include foods such as oranges, sweet potatoes, legumes.\n\n

** You will also need calcium, so include .\n\n
1.Dairy products.\n
2.Dark and green leafy vegetables, broccoli, asparagus among others.\n\n

** To help you deal with morning sickness, include .\n\n
1.Soups between meals. \n
2.Ginger, food rich in carbs and protein.\n\n

** Sugarcane juice is a rich source of nutrients like Vitamin A, magnesium, potassium and iron. It offers instant energy and is an immunity booster.
        

    </string>

    <string name="secondtrimester">
        *Add in good fats such as\n\n
1.Avocado, salmon and fish liver oil in your diet.\n
2.Foods with iron, meats, whole grain, dried fruits and legumes.\n\n

**During the fifth month, your growing baby will need Vitamin C so include:\n\n
1.Oranges and tomatoes in your daily diet.\n\n

**By the sixth month,\n\n
1.Add a lot of protein rich food like lean meat, fish, eggs, tofu. \n
2.Necessary carbohydrates food such as sweet potatoes, whole wheat pasta, sweet corn, seeds, legumes and nuts, oats.\n\n

**Pregnant women should avoid foods sweetened with refined sugar and opt for fruits with low-glycemic index**
        


    </string>


    <string name="thirdtrimester">
      **For this crucial time, youll need these five nutrients:\n\n
1.Vitamin C, calcium, magnesium, Omega 3 fatty acids and choline.\n
2.Fresh fruits (berries, banana, melon etc).\n
3.Lentils, fresh green salad with radish, tomato, lettuce, beans and chickpeas.\n
4.Make sure to drink plenty of fluids to stay hydrated.\n
        

    </string>

    <string name="avoidfood">
        ***Food to be AVOIDED during pregnancy***\n\n
1.Fish and Seafood.\n
2.Papaya.\n
3.Eggplant or brinjal.\n
4.Unpasteurized Milk and its Products.\n
5.Sesame Seeds.\n
6.Ajinomoto(mainly contained in chinese food/ street food).\n
7.Pineapple.\n
8.Refined Flour Products(bread,noodles,pasta,pizza(products made out of maida)).\n
9.Grapes.
    </string>


    <string name="firstmonthset">

       Breast milk or formula "ONLY"




    </string>

    <string name="secondmonthset">

    1.Breast milk or formula.\n
    2.Pureed foods and iron-fortified infant cereal if your doctor gives the okay.\n\n
        #How much per day\n

    1.Begin with about 1 teaspoon pureed food or cereal. Mix cereal with 4 to 5 teaspoons breast milk or formula. (It will be very runny)\n
    2.Increase to 1 tablespoon of pureed food, or 1 tablespoon of cereal mixed with breast milk or formula, twice a day. If you\'re giving cereal, gradually thicken the consistency by using less liquid.\n

        ##Feeding tips\n

    --->Introduce new foods one at a time. Wait two or three days, if possible, before offering another new food. (Wait three days if your baby or family has a history of allergies.) It\'s also a good idea to write down the foods your baby samples. If she has an adverse reaction,a food log will make it easier to pinpoint the cause.\n
    --->The order in which you introduce new foods doesn\'t usually matter. Your child\'s doctor can advise you.


    </string>

    <string name="thirdmonthset">

    1.Breast milk or formula.\n
    2.Pureed fruits and vegetables.\n
    3.Iron-fortified infant cereal.\n
    4.Pureed meat or tofu.\n
    5.Pureed beans or legumes.\n
    6.Unsweetened yogurt.\n\n

##How much per day\n\n

    1.One teaspoon fruit, gradually increased to 2 or 3 tablespoons in four feedings\n
    2.One teaspoon vegetables, gradually increased to 2 or 3 tablespoons in four feedings\n
    3.Three to Nine tablespoons cereal in 2 or 3 feedings\n


    </string>

    <string name="fourthmonthset">

    1.Breast milk or formula.\n
    2.Mashed fruits and vegetables.\n
    3.Pureed meat, fish, or tofu.\n
    4.Mashed beans or legumes.\n
    5.Yogurt and soft pasteurized cheese.\n
    6.Finger food (O-shaped cereal, small pieces of ripe banana, scrambled eggs, well-cooked pieces of potato, cut-up bagels).\n
    7.Iron-fortified cereal(barley, wheat, oats, mixed cereals).\n\n

##How much per day\n\n

    1.One-fourth to One-third cup dairy (or 1/2 ounce cheese).\n
    2.One-fourth to Half cup iron-fortified cereal.\n
    3.Three_fourth to One cup fruit.\n
    4.Three_fourth to One cup vegetables.\n
    5.Three to Four tablespoons protein-rich food.\n


    </string>

    <string name="fifthmonthset">

    1.Breast milk or formula.\n
    2.Chopped or bite-size fruits and vegetables.\n
    3.Yogurt, soft pasteurized cheese, cottage cheese (no cow\'s milk until age 1).\n
    4.Protein (small bits of meat, poultry, boneless fish, tofu, and well-cooked beans).\n
    5.Mashed beans or legumes.\n
    6.Finger food (O-shaped cereal, small pieces of ripe banana, scrambled eggs, well-cooked pasta, cut-up bagels).\n
    7.Combo foods (macaroni and cheese, casseroles).\n
    8.Iron-fortified cereal(barley, wheat, oats, mixed cereals).\n\n

##How much per day\n\n

    1.One-third cup dairy (or 1/2 ounce cheese).\n
    2.One-fourth to Half cup iron-fortified cereal.\n
    3.Three-fourth to One cup fruit.\n
    4.Three-fourth to One cup vegetables.\n
    5.1/8 to 1/4 cup combo foods.\n
    6.Three to Four tablespoons protein-rich food.\n


    </string>

    <string name="applyfbnc">

        ***No Registration is Required ****\n\n
        This scheme is releted to improvement of medical facilities at government hospitals.



    </string>

    <string name="applyhbnc">
        **Get Registered yourself with ASHA (similar to Aanganwadi Workers) within your vicinity.\n\n
        **Requirement:\n
        Any Government Identity Proof.\nBPL Certificate (mandatory)


    </string>
    <string name="applyinap">



    </string>
    <string name="applyjssk">

      **Get Registered yourself in near by PHC(Primary Health Center) or any Government Health institute.\n\n
      **Requirement:\n
        Any Government Identity Proof.\nBPL Certificate (mandatory)


    </string>
    <string name="applyrbsk">

        **First level of Screening is done at Delivery Points through existing medical officers.\n
        **Second Screening of NEW BORN is done by ASHA workers at home.\n
        **Regular Monitoring of Child for the next few months by Aanganwadi workers.\n
        **Once the Child is screened and referred from any otf these above points of identification , then child will be eligible for treatment at ZERO cost to family.



    </string>

    <string name="feedback">

        \"Please provide your valuable feedback\"
    </string>


</resources>
